<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="title_activity_help">Help</string>
    <string name="title_activity_topic">Help Topic</string>

    <string name="no_help_available">
      There is no help available at this time.
    </string>
    <string name="about_help_topics">
      Help is available for each section of this app.
    </string>

    <string name="help_page_intro">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1 style="text-align:center"><font color="#ff3333"><b>Roman Numeral Converter</b></font></h1>
            <p style="text-align:center"> For information on the different parts of this app, touch one of the images below:</p>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section1">Numerals</string>
    <string name="help_text_section1">
        <![CDATA[
            <p><font color="#003366">Roman Numerals can be used to represent any Arabic Numeral between 1 and 3999. Find out more here&#8230;</font></p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section1">
        <![CDATA[
            <h5>Roman Numerals can be used to represent any Arabic Numeral between 1 and 3999, are
                generally are written in descending order from left to right, and are added sequentially.</h5>
            <tt> &emsp;Roman&emsp;Arabic<br>
                &emsp;&emsp; I&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1<br>
                &emsp;&emsp; V&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;5<br>
                &emsp;&emsp; X&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;10<br>
                &emsp;&emsp; L&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;50<br>
                &emsp;&emsp; C&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;100<br>
                &emsp;&emsp; D&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;500<br>
                &emsp;&emsp; M&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;&emsp;1000<br>
            </tt>
            <br>
            <p>For example MMVI (2006) is interpreted as 1000 + 1000 + 5 + 1<br><br>
            Certain combinations employ a subtractive principle which specifics that where a symbol
            of smaller value preceded a symbol of larger value, the smaller value is subtracted from
            the larger value, and the result is added to the total. <br><br>
            For example, in MCMXLIV (1944) the symbols C,X and I each precede a symbol of higher value,
            and the results is interpreted as 1000 plus (1000 minus 100) plus (50 minus 10) plus (5 minus 1)<br><br>
            In addition to the additive and subtractive principles, there are also rules covering repetition of various symbols. <br><br>
            For example, the Symbols I, X, C and M can be repeated up to three times in succession for addition, but no more. <br><br>
            D, L and V can never be repeated.<br><br>
            For subtraction, symbols cannot be repeated.<br><br>
            And to further complicate the representation:<br>
                &emsp;&emsp;I can be subtracted from V and X only;<br>
                &emsp;&emsp;X can be subtracted from L and C only;<br>
                &emsp;&emsp;C can be subtracted from D and M only;<br>
                &emsp;&emsp;V, L and D can never be subtracted</p>
            <br>
			<p>Check out the Wikipedia entries for a lot more details on both Roman and Arabic Numerals:</p>
			<p align="center">
			&emsp;<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Roman_numerals"><font color="#4b1f6f"><b>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Roman_numerals</b></font></a>
			<br>
			&emsp;<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arabic_numerals"><font color="#4b1f6f"><b>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arabic_numerals</b></font></a>
			<br><br><\p>
            <h5>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</h5>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section2">Manual Mode</string>
    <string name="help_text_section2">
         <![CDATA[
            <h3 style="text-align:center"><font color="#6B78B4"><b>MANUAL MODE</b></font></h3>
            <p> Learn how to operate the application in manual conversion mode&#8230;</p>
         ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section2">
        <![CDATA[
            <h3 style="text-align:center"><font color="#6B78B4"><b>MANUAL MODE</b></font></h3>
            <p>Enter either a Roman or Arabic Numeral in the editable fields and the conversion takes place! <br><br>
            If successful you will see “DONE” in the status field.  <br><br>
            If problems, you will see “FAILED” in the status field with a failure reason underneath.<br><br>
            Tap the status text “READY/DONE/FAILED” to reset both editable fields<br><br>
            Long press the status text to switch to AUTO-COUNT mode
            </p>
            <h5>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</h5>
        ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="help_title_section3">Auto Mode</string>
    <string name="help_text_section3">
        <![CDATA[
            <h3 style="text-align:center"><font color="#6B78B4"><b>AUTO MODE</b></font></h3>
            <p> Learn how to take advantage of automated counting to see how Arabic numerals convert to Roman&#8230;</p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section3">
        <![CDATA[
            <h3 style="text-align:center"><font color="#6B78B4"><b>AUTO MODE</b></font></h3>
            <p> Let the app take the strain! Increment or decrement a counter with the buttons –
            see the equivalent Roman and Arabic Numeral representations immediately.   <br><br>
            Long press the Increment/Decrement buttons to increase step size to 10 rather than default 1. <br><br>
            Hit the “COUNT” button and watch the counter automatically tick over – long press to switch
            direction between counting upwards and counting downwards. <br><br>
            Tap the status text “AUTO” to reset the counter<br><br>
            Long press the status text to switch back to MANUAL mode<br><br>
            </p>
            <h5>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</h5>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section4">About</string>
    <string name="help_text_section4">
         <![CDATA[
            <h3 style="text-align:center"><font color="#6B78B4"><b>ABOUT</b></font></h3>
            <p> Details about this Roman Numeral Converter application&#8230;</p>
         ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section4">
        <![CDATA[
            <h3 style="text-align:center"><font color="#6B78B4"><b>ABOUT</b></font></h3>
            <p>Roman Numeral Converter     v1.1     December 2014<br><br>
            Expanded from a programming exercise – not exhaustive tested on all devices!<br><br>
            Email feedback/ideas/comments to
            <a href="mailto:shauncotter00@gmail.com?subject=RomanNumeralConverter%20Feedback">shauncotter00@gmail.com</a>
            </p>
            <h5>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</h5>
        ]]>
    </string>

</resources>
